aprokocity.com 2016-10-24

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to **Aprokocity.com** , an interactive online news service operated by Inbrand Nig limited. We are dedicated to preserving and safeguarding your privacy during your visit to our site and we are committed to protecting your personal identifiable information you may provide us through our Website.

This Privacy Policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you. We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through our Website

**Use of Cookies and Web beacons**

We gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers. Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

Similarly to the above, we, and our third party service providers may gather information about your general Internet use by using a cookie file. “Cookies” are files that can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information. Cookies manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on our site. Cookies can either remain on your computer until you delete them or they may last only until you close your browser. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.

In addition, we may also use “Web beacons” that monitor your use of our Sites. Web beacons are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a Web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server.

**Managing Cookies and Web Beacons**

All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

Our website contain advertising, and our advertisers may also use cookies. They do this to provide a better user experience, for example by keeping track of which advertisements have been served to which users. If you decline cookies you may see more advisements, or more repeat advertisements than a user that accepts cookie.

**Use of Your Information**

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. To provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such information.

To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.

Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.

**Keeping Your Personal Data secure**

While we take every reasonable to step to ensure data security, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you or where you have chosen a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

**Third Party Links**

You mind find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

**Contacting Us**

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us:

General Enquiries: feedback@aprokocity.com

Advert Orders: adverts@aprokocity.com
